{
    "subject": "resource/Spain",
    "predicate": "property/timeZone",
    "object": "CET",
    "human_readable": "The time zone of Spain is CET.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8714767098426819,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of events or activities that might be affected by the CET time zone in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8127698302268982,
            "question": "How might the CET time zone affect travel plans to Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7885748744010925,
            "question": "What implications does the CET time zone have for businesses operating in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7151473164558411,
            "question": "What time zone does Spain use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6005135178565979,
            "question": "What is the abbreviation for the time zone used in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5922075510025024,
            "question": "During daylight saving time, does Spain change its time zone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5041168332099915,
            "question": "Is Spain in a different time zone than most of Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3823022246360779,
            "question": "If it is 10:00 AM in London, what time would it be in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34277424216270447,
            "question": "How many hours ahead is Spain from Greenwich Mean Time (GMT) during standard time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25725826621055603,
            "question": "What does CET stand for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The time zone of Spain is CET.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8406_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many hours ahead is Spain from Greenwich Mean Time (GMT) during standard time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8406_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If it is 10:00 AM in London, what time would it be in Spain?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8406_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Spain in a different time zone than most of Europe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8406_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8406_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents clearly state that Spain falls within the Central European Time Zone (CET) during Standard Time and Central European Summer Time (CEST) during Daylight Saving Time. This confirms that the time zone of Spain is indeed CET, making the triple correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents confirm that Spain operates on Central European Time (CET) during standard time and Central European Summer Time (CEST) during daylight saving time, which supports the statement \"The time zone of Spain is CET.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}